<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentations on Dan Feeny</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentations on Dan Feeny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Guest Lecturer - Kwantlen Polytechnic University</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/kpu_lecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/kpu_lecture/</guid>
      <description>I was a guest lecturer at Kwantlet Polytechnic University for the Technical Management and Services Program&amp;rsquo;s TMAS5110 - &amp;ldquo;Managing Technical Business Growth. I presented a lecture and discussion on &amp;ldquo;Leadership Styles&amp;rdquo; that I had originally created the Tribe Leadership Collaboration Group.&#xA;After the topic drew to a close, I invited the class to ask questions about the Tech Industry in general which led to some great discussions with potential future leaders of Vancouver Tech scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guest Speaker for SFU&#39;s Object Technology Program</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/sfu_otp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/sfu_otp/</guid>
      <description>I was invited to represent Infowave&amp;rsquo;s partnership SFU&amp;rsquo;s Object Technology Program class of 2002. I spoke to the students of that year&amp;rsquo;s program in an auditorium about what they could expect day-to-day in a software engineering job and answered any questions they may have had. This partnership also provided another source of candidates for hiring in a difficult market.&#xA;I was also asked to review the curriculum and was able to provide feedback on missing elements - specifically SCM concepts: Source Control, Build Management, Version Management, and Configuration Management.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
