<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Projects on Dan Feeny</title>
    <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Projects on Dan Feeny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:21:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Text Support Solution for the Pacific Post Partum Support Society</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/icarol-sms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:21:21 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/icarol-sms/</guid>
      <description>In late 2017, the Pacific Post Partum Support Society (PPPSS) conducted a trial texting support program to measure the impact of providing post partum support through text message interactions. What was discovered was that phone support metrics did not change and a new demographic of parents were taking advantage of the service - a group of people who were previously not being given the support they needed through a difficult time in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeny Technology Solutions</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/feeny-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:47:43 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/feeny-tech/</guid>
      <description>Feeny Technology Solutions was a boutique technology coaching and IT company I started as a teenager specializing in one-on-one technology consulting, guidance and support for individuals and small businesses. I purposesly kept my client list small in order to provide a very dedicated, close relationship with my customers. This also ensured the business did not distract from my day job as a software engineer and eventual technology leader.&#xA;Respecting some of my residential customers&amp;rsquo; privacy, some of my customers included:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaspberryPi-based IR Camera outputting a Timelapse video</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/timelapse-picamera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/timelapse-picamera/</guid>
      <description>More details coming.&#xA;But in the meantime, here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of a timelapse video created by this quick little project. Note that the purple hue is due to the IR camera designed to record foliage in low light conditions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
