<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Professional Projects on Dan Feeny</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Professional Projects on Dan Feeny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RBC Alternate Mortgage System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/rbc-ams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/rbc-ams/</guid>
      <description>The success of our launch of Lendesk&amp;rsquo;s Lender Network, a platform that allows licensed mortgage brokerages to file applications directly to lenders, was proving to be attractive to mortgage brokers. We signed a statement of work to provide RBC&amp;rsquo;s alternative lending division an integration with their traditional mortgage platform (LINK). This integration automatically ingested mortgage applications from customers that were referred to RBC&amp;rsquo;s alternative mortgage specialists. Those specialists could then take advantage of Lendesk&amp;rsquo;s mortgage workflow platform and effortlessly submit those applications to Lendesk&amp;rsquo;s Lender Network, including Scotiabank, First National, CMLS, Equitable Bank, and the Paradigm Quest group of lenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guildford Rewards Payment Gateway and Mobile Apps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/guildford-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/guildford-rewards/</guid>
      <description>I led the team responsible for developing Ivanhoe Cambridge&amp;rsquo;s new loyalty and gift card program. This consisted of payment gateway services, a rule-based payment and rewards engine, an accompanying desktop portal, and mobile apps for Android and iPhone.&#xA;We added a number of new-to-Paywith features and platform enhancements for this project including:&#xA;A new simplified onboarding flow on the web and mobile apps An SMS-based sign-up flow Rewards campaigns - time-bound loyalty and rewards rules A set of new discounts and rebates rules requested by Ivanhoe Cambridge (owner of Guildford Towne Centre) Welcome gifts on sign-up A new rules-based offer engine service A new rules-based communication service The introduction of multi-factor authentication (SMS-based) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INETCO Analytics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/inetco-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/inetco-analytics/</guid>
      <description>INETCO Analytics was a green-field project using INETCO Insight&amp;rsquo;s firehose of real-time, financial transactional data to gain valuable and actionable insights to grow your business. Boeing Employee Credit Union (BECU) was one of the first customers to deploy this new product. This product helped Boeing:&#xA;Deliver an exceptional member experience through a deepened understanding of ATM usage and improved responsiveness — Achieved a 78.9% ATM Net Promoter Score and a 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivonet Kiosk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/vivonet-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/vivonet-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Kiosk NEXTEP - Our team was challenged to release a tablet-based, self-serve ordering system that could handle the demands of restaurants at the Dallas Fort Worth (DFW) airport - and we were asked to do it in a matter of months. We rose to the challenge. Building on and enhancing the Mobile ordering system, and creating a brand new tablet ordering interface, we created and deployed the working system to DFW in under 3 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Builds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/rocket-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/rocket-build/</guid>
      <description>At Rocket, I was selected to start a new Software Configuration Management department, picking or hiring the members, and strengthening our engineering practices across all teams. Growing the team to 4 members, we focused on the areas of build management, branch management, version management, and release management. Our achievements included:&#xA;Wrangling multiple branches of source code across multiple teams with varying feature sets into a single, organized set of branches representing our software lifecycle process stages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Casino-wide Multiplayer Class 3 Gaming Server for Slot Machines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/class-3-gaming-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/class-3-gaming-server/</guid>
      <description>More detail of the actual gaming server on its way!&#xA;Red Hawk Gaming was a company contracted by the Miami Tribe of Oklahoma owned Rocket Gaming Systems. Rocket was an indigenous owned company that built casino games and systems sold and installed to casino operators throughout the U.S. Red Hawk developed all the software for Rocket in its Vancouver office while hardware was developed in Rocket&amp;rsquo;s Grove, Oklahoma office.&#xA;I joined the team responsible for developing the C++ based server software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office Doc Attachments Display Service for Early Mobile Web Devices</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/msoffice-mobile-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/msoffice-mobile-web/</guid>
      <description>In 2000, mobile data technology was just beginning to sprout in the business world. Microsoft was working on Windows Mobile while Palm were the darling of keyboard warriors. Before desktop VPN standards had made the jump to mobile devices, Infowave was ahead of its time creating connectors that gave mobile devices access to companies&amp;rsquo; resources with their firewalls - extending applications previously only available while on-site to the mobile workers of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Arm 2&#39;s Mobile Base System Payload Orbital Accomodator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/mbs-poa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/contributions/mbs-poa/</guid>
      <description>More detail on its way!&#xA;The Canada Arm 2 project was a robotic arm installed on the International Space Station. It remains in operation today performing a variety of tasks from loading and unloading cargo modules to assisting extra vehicular activities by astronauts during station maintenance tasks. MDA was responsible for the command and control software that drove the 3 major pieces of the arm: the Space Station Remote Manipulator System (SSRMS), Mobile Base System (MBS), and Special Purpose Dextrous Manipulator (SPDM but later renamed &amp;ldquo;Dextre&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
