<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>React on Dan Feeny</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/react/</link>
    <description>Recent content in React on Dan Feeny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/react/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RBC Alternate Mortgage System</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/contributions/rbc-ams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/contributions/rbc-ams/</guid>
      <description>The success of our launch of Lendesk’s Lender Network, a platform that allows licensed mortgage brokerages to file applications directly with lenders, proved to be attractive to mortgage brokers. We signed a statement of work to provide RBC’s alternative lending division with an integration to their traditional mortgage platform (LINK). This integration automatically ingested mortgage applications from customers referred to RBC’s alternative mortgage specialists. These specialists could then take advantage of Lendesk’s mortgage workflow platform and effortlessly submit those applications to Lendesk’s Lender Network, including Scotiabank, First National, CMLS, Equitable Bank, and the Paradigm Quest group of lenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guildford Rewards Payment Gateway and Mobile Apps</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/contributions/guildford-rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/contributions/guildford-rewards/</guid>
      <description>I led the team responsible for developing Ivanhoe Cambridge&amp;rsquo;s new loyalty and gift card program. This consisted of payment gateway services, a rule-based payment and rewards engine, an accompanying desktop portal, and mobile apps for Android and iPhone.&#xA;We added a number of new-to-Paywith features and platform enhancements for this project including:&#xA;A new simplified onboarding flow on the web and mobile apps An SMS-based sign-up flow Rewards campaigns - time-bound loyalty and rewards rules A set of new discounts and rebates rules requested by Ivanhoe Cambridge (owner of Guildford Towne Centre) Welcome gifts on sign-up A new rules-based offer engine service A new rules-based communication service The introduction of multi-factor authentication (SMS-based) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
